Chezia Verdiana Adi

I enjoy working in creative fields as much as doing research and dealing with numbers. The idea of extracting the essence of complex data and turning it into a clear, reader-friendly report has been my current obsession. Working in a fast-paced environment in which time is a crucial variable, I learned ways to automate my dashboard in order to deliver such report precisely on time.



Personal Info:

Jakarta, Indonesia 28 October 1996 chezvdna@gmail.com +62 812 8036 0802

Skills:

Microsoft Office Google Sheets Adobe Photoshop HTML, CSS, JavaScript Basic UX Research Basic SEO SQL

Social:

Bē Chezia Verdiana
in Chezia Adi

Portfolio:

behance.net/chezvdna bit.ly/chezportfolio

Languages:

Bahasa Indonesia

Mother Language

English

Professional TOEFL 600

French

Basic Conversation

DELF A1

Experience:

08/2019 - Present Junior OTA Performance Manager

PT. OYO Rooms Indonesia Responsibilities:

Manage 400+ properties' performance in assigned hub(s)
 Create and deliver action plan and progress report

- Create dashboard and tracker on spreadsheet

- Analyze market potential and deliver marketing strategy

- Coordinate with revenue managers to maximize occupancy

and GMV

Achievement:
- Generate an average of IDR 60 billion revenue per month

- Target achievement always above 80%

03/2019 - 08/2019 OTA Support

PT. OYO Rooms Indonesia Responsibilities:

- Assist OTA Performance Manager on their daily task

2018 - 03/2019 Freelance Designer

Spire Research - Kementerian Perindustrian RI

Flash interactive video
 Infographic poster

Absolute Inc.

- Website design (Landing Page)

Education:

2014 - 2018 Universitas Padjadjaran

Sarjana Hubungan Internasional

- GPA: 3.31

- Thesis: Celebrity Diplomacy

(Soft Power, Branding, Media, Popular Culture)

2011 - 2014 Charis National Academy

Senior High School

- Student of the Year (2013 & 2014)

- Played theatrical performing of "Taming of the Shrew" by

Shakespeare

Certification & Courses:

2020 Web Development

M₁M₀

2020 Basic SEO

Hacktiv8

2020 Basic UX Research

Skill Academy